PROGRAMMING ASSIGNMENT:

Create an IOS application that has the following requirements in Swift.
The program's primary functionality is to sort a string with the input from a user.

Example input: befdac
Expected output: abcdef

The user interface will contain the following four elements:
1. A textbox that allows the user to input a string
2. A control (for instance a combobox) that selects the strategy to use for sorting the string.
3. A button that will sort the string using the selected strategy.
4. A label where the output will be shown (the sorted string)

The FOCUS of the assignment is on implementing the DESIGN PATTERNS.
a) Strategy pattern: is a software design pattern that enables an algorithm's behavior to be selected at
runtime. The strategy pattern will be used for sorting the strings in 2 different implementations. You can
choose two of these sorting methods: BubbleSort, QuickSort, or MergeSort.

b) For the logic and view part of the application, it will be implemented in the Model-View-Controller
pattern and you are not allowed to use a framework for this.

Make sure to follow proper development practices, and so ensure that all validations are in place.

Do an automated test of the individual components of your code to gain an advantage